

Rauno Harkmann

CV_Rauno_Harkmann

Male • 01 Apr 1987 5512695 rauno.harkmann@gmail.com

SUMMARY

I am hard worker with a positive attitude and wide range of working experience from military field to print shops. I am athletic and fast learner and adapt well in different situations.

I would not limit any fields for my next challenge as long as this is in Web development. I have recently completed a hands-on Javascript and React front end development 12-week cource.

It is important to me that the work I do would create value to the company and would include room for development through the career.

I am ready for completely new challenges as well and for retraining.

I value team effort but am also able to succeed happily in individual tasks.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Specialist

KAITSEVÄGI • Estonia

www.ksk.edu.ee

Aug 2020 - Oct 2022 • 2 y. and 3 m

Security

The job responsibilities included being responsible for equipment management and ordering equipment in the Axapta program, and using Microsoft Office (Word and Excel) programs in daily work.

Instructor

Milrem OÜ • Estonia

Mar 2019 - Apr 2020 • 1 y. and 2 m

Manufacturing / Production

Junior instructor. Main duties were creating manuals and training materials, conducting training internally and for our international clients on unmanned ground vehicles. But also participating in developing our product as a military specialist and also search and purchase of instructors gear and equipment.

Layoff due to the economic situation related to the corona crisis.

Operator

DIGITRÜKK OÜ/ DIGIPRINT • Estonia

Jul 2015 - Feb 2019 • 3 y. and 8 m

Manufacturing / Production

Production worker at the print shop. Main duties were working on the large format printer and helping in other phases of production as per need (assembling trade fair exhibitions and boxes, post-processing etc)

Operator

ILOTRÜKK • Estonia

Apr 2013 - Jul 2015 • 2 y. and 4 m

Manufacturing / Production

Production worker at the print shop. Main duties were working on the guillotine and other preparations for production. And also helping in other phases of production as per need.

Soldier

Scoutspataljon • Estonia

Jan 2008 - Apr 2013 • 5 y. and 4 m

Public / Governmental Service

Accomplishments three deployments to Afghanistan 2009 as an anti tank assistant, 2010 as a machine gunner, 2012 as a gunner. My contribution was awarded with a medal public institute.

Soldier

KAITSEVÄGI • Estonia

www.ksk.edu.ee

Jan 2008 - Dec 2008 • 1 y.

Public / Governmental Service

Time service. Completed junior noncommissioned officer course. Sergeant rank

EDUCATION

Pärnumaa Kutsehariduskeskus (Estonia, Vocational education)

Ehitusviimistlus

2003 - 2006

LANGUAGE SKILLS

	Listening	Reading	Spoken interaction	Spoken production	Writing
Estonian (Language o	of communication)				
Estonian	C2	C2	C1	C1	C1
English	B2	B2	B2	B2	B2

Levels: A1/A2:Basic user - B1/B2: Independent user - C1/C2: Proficient user

COMPUTER SKILL

OFFICE SOFTWARE

Advanced MS Word, MS PowerPoint, MS Outlook, MS Excel

PROGRAMMING LANGUAGES

Intermediate JavaScript, React

GRAPHICS, DESIGN, MULTIMEDIA

Beginner Adobe Illustrator

DRIVING SKILLS

Driving licence since Acquired driving license categories

2015 **B**

DESIRED POSITION

Public / Governmental Service

specialist

WORK TYPE:

employee

WORKING TIME:

Full-time

LOCATIONS:

Tallinn

OTHER

ADVANCED TRAINING

JavaScript & React: From Zero to Specialist Intensive Course

Aurora Development OÜ • Estonia

2023 • 12 weeks

Additional information about the course: https://development.ee/javascript-react-nullist-front-end-spetsialistiks-intensiivope-ohtune/

Certificate is being created, course ended June 29th, 2023

REFERENCES

Raido Saremat • Former employer • Milrem OÜ • Juhtiv väljaõppe spetsialist • 5101025 • raido.saremat@milrem.com

ADDITIONAL INFO

A man with good communication skills, hardworking, conscientious and quick to adapt wants to find a challenging job.